wink.com 2014-12-31

# MyLife | Connecting everyone. All in one place.

MyLife.com, Inc. (“we”, “us”, “our”, or “MyLife”) recognizes the importance of consumer privacy and we take this issue seriously. This Online Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) has been designed in a format that is easy to navigate and read so that you can clearly understand our privacy practices with respect to the information collected by websites and other online interfaces that are owned or operated by MyLife and contain a link to this Policy (collectively, the “Services”). We are committed to treating your Personal Information (as defined below) with care and respect.

This Policy — together with the [User Agreement](http://www.mylife.com/user-agreement/), which are incorporated herein by reference — describes how we collect, use, and disclose information on or through the Services. Please note that the Policy does not apply to activities that are “offline” or unrelated to the Services unless otherwise expressly set forth below. By accessing or interacting with the Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of the Policy.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

MyLife and its service providers collect two main types of information through the Services: Personal Information and Other Information.

**“Personal Information”** refers to information that can be used to contact you or identify you as a particular individual. The specific kinds of Personal Information we collect through the Services typically depend on the exact nature of our relationship with you, but might include:

  * Full name;
  * Address (e.g., postal, billing, shipping, etc.);
  * Telephone number including cell number;
  * Fax number;
  * E-mail address;
  * Date of birth;
  * Payment information (e.g., credit or debit card number, expiration date, other financial account details, etc.);
  * User ID, login name, screen name, nickname, or handle and password;
  * Social media accounts and/or IDs;
  * Likeness and physical characteristics (e.g., profile picture, eye and hair color, height, etc.); and
  * vDetails regarding background or preferences (e.g., interests, nicknames, favorite quote, etc.);
  * IP Address;
  * School, workplace and job position;
  * Criminal record

**“Other Information”** refers to any information that does not reveal your specific identity or directly relate to you as an individual. We collect a number of different types of Other Information through the Services, such as:

  * Browser and device information (e.g., browser/device type, UDID, geographic location, etc.);
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags, and other tracking technologies;
  * Demographic and other similar information you provide (e.g., gender, ethnicity, relationship status, etc.); and
  * Aggregated or otherwise de-identified information.

**HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION**

**_Personal Information_**

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information through the Services in a variety of ways, including:

  * **Voluntary Submissions.** We collect Personal Information from you when you elect to voluntarily provide it to us. For example, certain features of the Services are only accessible by individuals who have registered and created an account with MyLife (collectively, “Members”). In order to become a Member, you must first complete our [online registration form](http://www.mylife.com/showRegistration.pub), which requests basic contact information (e.g., name, date of birth, e-mail address, etc.) from you. You can also enter certain other details about yourself on your profile page (e.g., job and schools). The information you provide during the registration process allows MyLife to create a unique profile for you on the Services (your “Member Profile”), which may be supplemented with other information as described herein.

Other examples of ways that you may voluntarily provide Personal Information through the Services include: directly requesting information or assistance, inquiring about the Services, sending us an e-mail, connecting via a Social Network API, submitting a payment, completing other online forms (e.g., to add or update information in your Member Profile, to invite contacts to join the Services through our e-mail integration feature, to perform people searches through our Who’s Searching for You® feature, etc.), or otherwise interacting with MyLife’s online presence. To this end, the Services may provide you with the opportunity to share your reviews, thoughts, or comments regarding your relationship with MyLife. Such testimonial information may include your personal experiences with our products or services and related Personal Information that you choose to submit through the Services. In the event you elect to do so, we will request your permission before publicly posting any Personal Information contained therein on the Services. You can also request that we remove your testimonial any time by contacting Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST or visit our [HELP section](http://www.mylife.com/help/).

> If you use the Facebook Connect function to import information or to create your Member Profile, we will collect the following: your full name, gender and date of birth; email address; employment and education; certain Facebook profile details; relationships; photos / videos; and live stream feeds. Facebook profile information will not be imported into your Member Profile without your consent. We will share this information in the manner specified in this privacy policy. You can edit and/or update this information on the MyLife site whenever you choose by going to the Edit section of your profile and adjusting the information as you wish.
> 
> Please note that if you choose to provide us with Personal Information relating to other people, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy. You should also be aware that any Personal Information you submit through public areas of the Services (e.g., blogs, forums, people search pages, etc.) can be viewed, collected, and possibly used by others, both on the Services (e.g., to send you unsolicited messages) and potentially on third-party services to the extent permissible under this Policy. We encourage Members and non-Members to refrain from disclosing Personal Information within such public areas of the Services that they do not wish to share. If you would like additional details regarding the areas of the Services that may be publicly accessible, please do not hesitate to contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST or visit our [HELP section](http://www.mylife.com/help/).

  * **Third-Party Sources.** We may acquire Personal Information about you from other sources, such as: public databases, joint marketing partners, social media platforms, people with whom you are friends or have otherwise connected on social media platforms, and other third parties. We may append third parties’ information to the Member’s profile (e.g. previous address) and notify the Member of such information.

Although MyLife will not create a Member Profile for you unless you request that we do so, we also maintain a database of public domain information we have licensed from third-party sources for display and resale on the Internet. Please note that we may use this information to create public profiles for non-Members (“Public Profiles”), as well as to allow Members to add to their existing Member Profiles. Members and non-Members can use the Services to search for individuals from their past using various parameters, and the results of their searches may include public domain information from Public Profiles and/or Member Profiles. If people search for you on the Internet (e.g., through a third-party search engine like Google or Yahoo!), their search results may also include links to your Public Profile and/or Member Profile on the Services. Additional information regarding the choices and controls that may be available to you with respect to your Member Profile and/or Public Profile can be found in the Your Choices and Controls section of the Policy. A Member may take control of their Public Profile anytime by claiming the Public Profile.

**Other Information**

MyLife and its service providers also collect Other Information through the Services in a number of different manners, including automatically through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. We use this information in order to, among other things: permit the Services to function properly, evaluate how you interact with the Services, determine where you are located, support data analytics and research, and assist with the marketing and product development efforts of MyLife and our business partners. Please note that under certain circumstances we may combine the Other Information we collect through the Services (e.g., a Member’s geographical location) with Personal Information (e.g., the Member’s name). If we do so, MyLife will treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Policy for as long as it is remains combined and identifies you as a particular individual.

Examples of the ways in which we may collect Other Information from you include the following:

  * **Cookies.** Cookies are small pieces of data that are based on your Internet activity and stored on the hard drive of your computer by your Internet browser when you visit a website. Through the use of cookies, we are able to collect traffic, usage, and other similar information about your interactions with the Services (e.g., time spent on the Services, the specific portions of the Services that you use or visit, language preferences, etc.), as well as recognize your computer or device to facilitate your use of the Services (e.g., to display information more efficiently). We may use this type of information for a variety of purposes, including: analyzing usage patterns, monitoring and improving the Services, personalizing your interactions with the Services, tracking Internet activity, and supporting our marketing efforts. When you visit the Services or other websites where we advertise, we or a third party may use Other Information collected through the Services to show you interest-based advertisements and offers that we think will be more relevant to your preferences and behaviors. Cookies enable us to personalize these advertisements and track their frequency and placement.  
Although most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you can generally find a “help” section on the browser toolbar that will inform you how to configure your browser settings to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or to reject cookies entirely. If you disable cookies, however, you will not have access to many features that make your interactions with the Services more efficient and some of the Services’ features may not function properly.
  * **Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technologies.** A web beacon (sometimes referred to as a “pixel tag” or a “clear GIF”) is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a website, e-mail, or other communication. Web beacons are typically one-pixel, transparent images and are used to transfer an individual’s unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database in order to associate that individual with previously acquired information about him/her in a database. They allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that accesses the website on which the beacon appears, the URL of such a website, the time that such a website was viewed, the type of browser used to view such a website, and the information contained in any cookies set by the third party.  
We may use web beacons and other similar tracking technologies to help us better manage content on the Services by informing us what content is effective. For example, web beacons allow us to measure the success of our marketing campaigns by providing insight into the actions taken by users of the Services (e.g., compiling statistics about the rate at which certain marketing e-mails are opened by their intended recipients). These technologies may also be used to help us remember who you are and track your account preferences.
  * **Log Files.** As is true of most online services, we automatically collect and store certain Other Information in our server log files each time a user accesses the Services. This information may include, for example: computer or device IP address, Internet browser type, Internet Service Provider (“ISP”), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information for purposes such as: analyzing trends, administering the Services, tracking user activities on the Services, and gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole.
  * **Information You Provide.** We collect Other Information that you choose to voluntarily provide to us through the Services. For example, you may have the opportunity to submit your location or indicate your preferred means of communication with MyLife. Unless combined with Personal Information, the Other Information you may provide to us generally does not identify you or any other user of the Services as a particular individual.
  * **Aggregated Information.** Occasionally, MyLife will combine Personal Information and other data to create de-identified information about groups or particular types of individuals that access the Services. Such aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Services as an individual and is considered Other Information for the purposes of this Policy. As an example, we may aggregate Personal Information from many different users to calculate the percentage of our total user base who have a particular area code.

**_Interest-Based Advertising and Third Parties_**

MyLife has relationships with certain third-party service providers who place advertisements on our behalf on other websites, perform tracking and other similar functions for the Services and our advertisements, and assist us in providing you with customer support. We may share information with these companies in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy. In addition, they may automatically collect information about your interaction with the Services (e.g., IP address, Internet browser type, online activity, etc.) through the use of tracking technologies such as cookies and web beacons. Among other things, this information is typically used to present you with advertisements tailored to your interests and better understand how the Services are being used.

The use of tracking technologies by third parties on the Services is governed by their respective privacy policies, and is not controlled by this Policy. Some of these third-party companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers additional information regarding cookies and web beacons, as well as a single location to opt out of interest-based advertising from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.com](http://www.networkadvertising.com/)). You may also opt out of the use of certain cookies by MyLife’s third-party advertising partners by visiting <http://www.privacychoice.org/companies> or <http://aboutads.info/choices>. If you would like more information about interest-based advertising on the Services and to know your choices about not having this information used by our advertising partners, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**_Third-Party Websites and Services_**

The Services and certain communications you receive from MyLife may contain links to websites and/or other online content that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of any such third-party websites or online services are not covered by this Policy. MyLife cannot control the treatment of your information by these third parties, and their privacy practices likely differ from those described in the Policy. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy practices of any such third parties prior to disclosing any Personal Information to them. If you have any questions regarding their collection, use, or disclosure of your information, you must contact the relevant third party directly.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION BY MYLIFE**

MyLife uses the information we collect about you through the Services (including Personal Information) in order to, among other things:

  * Confirm and complete the transactions you request;
  * Operate, monitor, manage, improve, and expand the Services and/or our business activities;
  * Provide you with customer service support and other requested information or services;
  * Respond to your inquiries and resolve your problems or disputes;
  * Develop, enhance, and market our products and services or the products and services of third parties;
  * Communicate with you about your interactions with the Services and your MyLife account;
  * Provide you with promotional offers, administrative materials, and other related content (including interest-based advertising);
  * Personalize your content and experiences on the Services;
  * Allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests, or promotions upon your request (note that these activities may be sponsored by third parties and additional rules or disclosures may apply to the treatment of your Personal Information — we encourage you to carefully read the terms and conditions applicable to any sweepstakes, contests, or promotions prior to enrolling);
  * Facilitate social sharing, messaging, or other similar functionalities on the Services;
  * Protect the rights or property of MyLife or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, the [User Agreement](http://www.mylife.com/user-agreement), and other applicable agreements and policies); and
  * Comply with legal or other regulatory requirements.

We may also use your Personal Information for other purposes when you provide us with prior consent to use your information in such a manner. For example, we may use Personal Information in accordance with disclosures made available to you when you submit that information through the Services, or as otherwise disclosed in this Policy.

Please note that unless expressly stated herein, MyLife may use and disclose Other Information for any purposes allowed by applicable laws and regulations. Under certain circumstances we may combine Other Information (e.g., a Member’s geographical location) with Personal Information (e.g., the Member’s name). If we do so, MyLife will treat the combined information as Personal Information for as long as it is remains combined and identifies you as a particular individual.

**SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH OTHER COMPANIES**

We may share the Personal Information that is collected on or through the Services with third parties under certain circumstances, including the following:

  * **Authorized Disclosures.** We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties when you consent to a particular disclosure of your Personal Information. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to co-register with select third-party partners when you become a Member, and we will share your Personal Information with our co-registration partners if you choose to co-register with them. Likewise, we may share Personal Information with our third-party co-marketing partners if we believe they have an offer that would be of interest to you and you have provided us with consent to do so. It is important to note that once we share your information with another company, that information becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
  * **Compelled Disclosures.** On rare occasions, we may share your Personal Information when we reasonably believe that we are compelled to do so by government authorities or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable laws and regulations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas, court orders, etc.). MyLife may also share your Personal Information with third parties if we believe in good faith that disclosure is appropriate to protect our rights, property, or safety (including the enforcement of this Policy, the [User Agreement](http://www.mylife.com/user-agreement) and any other applicable agreements and policies), or to protect the rights, property, or safety of third parties.
  * **Agents & Service Providers.** MyLife may disclose Personal Information to our trusted agents and service providers so that they can perform requested services on our behalf. For example, we may engage third parties to assist with: website hosting, data analysis, marketing efforts, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, e-mail delivery, credit card processing, auditing, and other similar services. These entities are generally prohibited from using such information for purposes unrelated to providing MyLife with the requested services (e.g., using your Personal Information for their own direct marketing purposes).
  * **Change of Control Transactions.** In the event that we file for bankruptcy, or MyLife is (or substantially all of its assets are) acquired by a third party pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, liquidation, or similar business transfer, the Personal Information stored in our databases may be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Messaging & Social Sharing.** We may disclose your Personal Information to identify you to anyone to whom you choose to send messages through the Services (e.g., contacts that you invite to join the Services through our e-mail integration feature). In addition, if you choose to engage in social sharing activity (e.g., linking your social media account to your account on the Services), we may disclose your Personal Information to friends and contacts associated with your social media account, other website users, and your social media account provider. By linking your MyLife account and your social media account, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider and acknowledge and agree that the shared information will be governed by the applicable third party’s privacy policy. Please do not connect your social media account with your MyLife account or otherwise engage in social sharing on the Services if you would prefer that your Personal Information not be disclosed in this manner.
  * **Public Submissions.** Information and materials you submit to public areas of the Services (e.g., message boards, profile pages, blogs, forums, etc.) will become public information that may be available to users of the Services and to the general public. For example, if you create, claim, or register a Public Profile through the Services, the information associated with your Public Profile (including Personal Information) may be disclosed to Members and non-Members through the Services, as well as through third-party search engines and similar online services. We urge you to be careful when deciding to make Personal Information publicly accessible on the Internet, including through the public portions of the Services.
  * **Who’s Searching for You®.** If you search for another person while logged into the Services, we may share your search with third parties via our Who’s Searching for You® feature. This functionality allows MyLife to notify Members whenever a people search is submitted through the Services for somebody with a matching name, as well as who was responsible for initiating the search in question. MyLife may also notify Members in a similar manner if their profiles have been viewed by somebody while logged into the Services. If you do not want your search(es) to be made public, you can delete it anytime from the saved searches page. Once the search is deleted, Members will not be notified or see your search(es).
  * **Non-Personal Information.** MyLife may collect, use, and share Other Information in any manner not otherwise prohibited by this Policy, without additional notice or compensation to you.

You may be presented with additional opportunities to receive information and/or marketing materials from third parties when you interact with the Services. Please note that any information you elect to disclose to such entities will be subject to their established privacy practices, as MyLife is unable to control the privacy practices of third parties. We encourage you to always review the applicable privacy policies and terms of use maintained by third parties prior to disclosing information to them. In the event you do elect to receive promotional materials from third parties and later decide that you no longer wish to receive communications from that entity, you will need to contact the relevant third party directly to change your preferences.

**YOUR CHOICES AND CONTROLS**

MyLife strives to provide you with the ability to exercise certain choices and controls in connection with our treatment of your information. The particular choices and controls that may be available to you typically depend on the nature of your relationship with MyLife.

**Profile Information**

Members who are interested in accessing, correcting, or updating the Personal Information in their Member Profiles (including any information populated via social sharing functionality) can generally do so at any time through the Services.

MyLife also offers non-Members the ability to access, correct, or update the Personal Information in their Public Profiles by first claiming or registering the Public Profile in question through the Services’ Public Profile claiming feature. This feature enables individuals to take control of their Public Profiles by reasonably verifying their identity to MyLife. For example, you can answer a few simple questions or provide us with a valid credit card to confirm your name and address (note that your credit card will not be charged during this process). Once it has been successfully claimed, a Public Profile can be edited or updated — including the fields of data that are displayed. Additional details regarding how to claim a Public Profile, as well as answers to commonly asked questions (e.g., what to do if information is inaccurate), can be found in the [HELP section.](http://www.mylife.com/help/)

If you would like to request that we suppress or remove a Member Profile or a Public Profile from our active databases or claim ownership of a Member Profile, simply visit our [HELP](http://www.mylife.com/help/) section or contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST. Upon receipt of any such request, we will take reasonable steps to validate that you are the correct owner of the profile that is the subject of your request. This precaution is designed to protect our users and their privacy, and may require us to contact you for confirmation purposes. Following verification of profile ownership, we will try to comply with your suppression or removal request as soon as reasonably practicable; however, please be aware that due to recordkeeping, legal, and other similar considerations we may be required to retain achieved records of changed or suppressed information. As a result, we may be unable to remove certain information from our backup systems, or we may only be able to remove it after fulfilling applicable requirements.

**_Communication Preferences_**

If you elect to register for the Services and become a Member, we and our partners may contact you with promotional offers and other similar correspondences. MyLife provides Members with the ability to change their communication preferences at any time. Among other things, you may use this option to opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails or postal mail from us and our partners.

In addition to such promotional e-mails, MyLife offers all Members access to e-mail newsletters and e-mail updates (e.g., announcing special offers, new features on the Services, account activity, etc.) upon registration for the Services. These communications may contain material is promotional in nature, including offers from our marketing partners. Members can opt-out of receiving e-mail newsletters or updates that may contain promotional material by following the “unsubscribe” procedures at the bottom of the relevant communication. Alternatively, you may change your notification settings by or visiting the “Email Notification Settings” page.

Please note that MyLife reserves the right to contact you with transactional e-mails containing important information relating to your MyLife account or the Services (e.g., renewal notifications, general system or administrative messages, address confirmations, payment receipts, etc.) without offering you the opportunity to opt-out. Thus, even if you elect to unsubscribe from any promotional e-mails and promotionally-oriented newsletters or e-mail updates, you may continue to receive customary business communications from MyLife.

If you are a non-Member and are receiving MyLife marketing e-mails from which you would like to opt-out, please simply follow the “unsubscribe” procedures at the bottom of the relevant communication. Non-Members can also unsubscribe from all future MyLife e-mail communications by contacting Customer Care. Please note that it may take us 7 – 10 days to process any such opt-out requests.

**_Referral Information_**

If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about the Services, we will ask you for your friend’s name and e-mail address. MyLife will automatically send your friend an e-mail inviting him or her to visit the Services, as well as two additional reminder e-mails if he or she does not respond to our initial e-mail. MyLife stores this information on our systems and may use it for purposes such as: sending the referral e-mails you request, tracking the success of our referral program, and locating contacts across the Internet.

**DATA SECURITY, INTEGRITY, AND RETENTION**

Information collected through the Services is submitted to MyLife and/or our service providers, and is hosted and stored by us (or by service providers on our behalf) in databases on servers situated in the U.S. and/or internationally. By providing us with information through the Services, you consent to the processing of such information in any and all such locations, including the U.S., which may have different data protection laws than those of your country of residence.

Your privacy is very important to MyLife and we are committed to protecting your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. To this end, we have implemented reasonable physical, technical, and administrative security measures for the Services that comply with applicable industry standards. This includes our practice of encrypting sensitive information submitted through the Services (e.g., credit card information provided on our order forms) with secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology.

It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality of your username and password on the Services. You are responsible for all uses of your password, whether or not such use has been authorized by you. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your MyLife account, visit our [HELP](http://www.mylife.com/help/) section or contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST immediately.

Despite our efforts to protect your Personal Information, the transmission of data over the Internet inherently requires the use of systems under the control of third parties. As a result, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, or you would simply like additional information regarding how we store and protect data, please visit our [HELP](http://www.mylife.com/help/) section or contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

MyLife understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the interactive world. We do not use the Services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of thirteen (13) without parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, please do not send any information about yourself to us through the Services. The Services are not intended for use by children.

In the event that MyLife becomes aware that we have collected Personal Information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and other applicable laws and regulations. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should promptly contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our files.

**POLICY UPDATES**

We may, in our sole discretion, make changes to this Policy from time to time in order to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements, or for other purposes. The most recent version of the Policy will always be posted to the Services. If we do make any changes, we will also update the “Effective Date” legend at the top of this Policy and we may provide you with other forms of notice as well. We encourage you to review the Policy periodically to ensure that you understand how we collect, use, and share information through the Services.

Any changes to this Policy will become effective thirty (30) days after the posted revision date of the Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Services following such changes, you are agreeing to accept the terms of the revised Policy

## Mobile Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs your use of the software application “MyLife” (“Application”) for mobile devices that was created by MyLife.com, Inc. (“MyLife”) The Application is a mobile application that allows you to view newsfeeds of major social networks, your e-mail accounts, and the ability to send and receive e-mail messages, social posts, and comments. The Application also allows you to monitor your identity, search for people, see who is searching for you, and send and receive messages directly to other MyLife members. .

  Notwithstanding, the Mobile App is subject to the terms and conditions contained in [Apple’s Minimum Terms of Developer’s End-User License Agreement](http://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/appstore/dev/minterms/) and the [Android Market Developer Distribution Agreement](https://play.google.com/about/developer-distribution-agreement.html), and to the extent any term or condition in this Agreement contradicts the aforementioned developer agreements, the terms and conditions of the developer agreements shall govern. Any information that is provided to Apple Inc. or Google Inc. will not be deemed confidential by Apple Inc. or Google Inc. This Privacy Policy shall also be subject to the terms and conditions contained in Apple Inc.’s App Store or Google’s Android Market.

  **User Provided Information**

  The Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the Application. Registration with us is optional. However, please keep in mind that you may not be able to use some of the features offered by the Application unless you register with us.

  When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide the following:  
• First and last name  
• Email  
• Zip code (location)  
• Birthdate (age)

  We may also use the information you provided us to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices and marketing promotions.

  Personal information shared via other social network services (e.g. Facebook, Linkedin, etc.) may share with MyLife the personal information you have provided to that social network service. The social network service should give you the right to opt-out of this sharing.

  If you use the Facebook Connect function to import information or to create your Member Profile, we will collect the following: your full name, gender and date of birth; email address; employment and education; certain Facebook profile details; relationships; photos/videos; and live stream feeds. Facebook profile information will not be imported into your Member Profile without your consent. We will share this information in the manner specified in this privacy policy. You can edit and/or update this information on the Application whenever you choose by going to the Edit section of your profile and adjusting the information as you wish.

  Please note that if you choose to provide us with personal information relating to other people, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy. You should also be aware that any personal information you submit through public areas of the MyLife’s services (e.g., blogs, forums, people search pages, etc.) (“Services”) can be viewed, collected, and possibly used by others, both on the Services (e.g., to send you unsolicited messages) and potentially on third-party services to the extent permissible under this Policy. We encourage Members and non-Members to refrain from disclosing personal information within such public areas of the Services that they do not wish to share. If you would like additional details regarding the areas of the Services that may be publicly accessible, please do not hesitate to contact Customer Care toll-free at (888) 704-1900 Mon-Fri 6am-9pm PST or visit the [HELP](http://www.mylife.com/help) section of the Application.  
You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information. Without your request to delete such information, we may keep the data indefinitely.

  **Automatically Collected Information**

  We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

  Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

  We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly remove the information.

  **We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:**  
• As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;  
• When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;  
• With our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.  
• If MyLife.com, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.

  **Opt-Out Rights**

  You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.

  You can stop future collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. You can also request to opt-out via email, at [privacy@mylife.com](mailto:privacy@mylife.com). Please allow sufficient time for us to process your request.

  **Data Analytics**

  Analytics companies may access data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user.

  **Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information**

  We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at privacy@mylife.com and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.

  **Security**

  MyLife is committed to maintaining the security of information under our control. We have taken security measures, consistent with best industry practices, to protect your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place industry-accepted physical, technical and administrative practices to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

  **Changes**

  MyLife may revise and update the Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy with the last revised date and providing an alert upon opening the Application. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.

  **Your Consent**

  By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. “Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States’ privacy standards.

  **Other Terms and Conditions**

  Please review the [User Agreement](http://www.mylife.com/user-agreement/), which sets out other important terms of your use of the Application.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy or our privacy practices on the Services, please write to us at:

MyLife.com, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
914 Westwood Blvd. (#517)  
Los Angeles, CA 90024-2905  
You can also contact us via e-mail at [privacy@mylife.com](mailto:privacy@mylife.com), or by calling our Customer Care team at (888) 704-1900. Please note that e-mail communications are not always secure; accordingly, we request that you do not include credit card details or other sensitive information in your e-mails to us.

  Last updated: September 17, 2014

  Effective Date: October 17, 2014

© Copyright 2013, Pioneer. Created by Themeapt.
